24小时
第三季  第19集
前情提要
托尼 是我 有麻烦了
Tony, its me. We have a problem.
刚才确定有一名男子接触病毒后离开了酒店
We just determined a man who was exposed to the virus got out of the hotel
该死的 怎么会这样?
Son of a bitch. How'd that happen?
他是在增强警戒之前逃出去的
He must have slipped out right before we reinforced the perimeter.
好像他并不知道自己已接触病毒
Its likely he had no idea had been exposed.
如果不能在他病发前找到他 恐怕病毒会泛滥
If we dont find this guy before he becomes symptomatic, we might be looking at an outbreak.
你想要什么?
What do you want?
给你新任务
To give you your next assignment.
有个叫瑞恩·查佩尔的 反恐局的地区主管
There is a man named Ryan Chappelle, regional director of CTU.
我要他的命
I want him killed.
如果你不照他说的做 这个桑德斯会用病毒
This man Saunders has proven that he will use this virus
害死更多的人
to inflict mass casualties if you don't do what he says.
他还要拿全国人的安危要挟我多久?
How long am I supposed to let him hold this country hostage?
一直到我们抓到他
Until we catch him.
桑德斯打电话来提了新要求
Saunders called in with another demand.
他又要干什么?
What does he want now?
他要你的命
He wants you killed.
他威胁说如果7点以前我们不把你的尸体送到指定位置 他就释放病毒
Hes threatened to release the virus into the main population unless we deliver your body by 7:00 a.m.
我的上帝 杰克
My god, Jack.
他已证明会继续放毒 总统别无选择
He has proven he will use the virus. The president didn't have a choice.
瑞恩 我们找到桑德斯了
Ryan, I think we found Saunders.
45分钟前他刚在那里打过电话
45 minutes ago he made a call from an apartment not far from here.
蔡斯正率队过去
Chase is leading a strike team over there now.
太好了 杰克
Good, Jack.
里面没人
No one is here.
桑德斯 你为何要如此?
Saunders, why are you doing this?
告诉你 你也不明白
Even if I told you, you wouldnt understand.
一会有辆货车过来
A van will be arriving shortly.
把查佩尔的尸体留给司机
Leave Chappelles body with the driver.
我很抱歉 瑞恩 我们必须这么做
I am sorry, Ryan, we got to do this.
跪下
Get on your knees.
很抱歉 我们辜负了你 瑞恩
I am sorry we let you down, Ryan.
上帝宽恕我
God forgive me.
以下事件发生于7点至8点之间
The following takes place between 7:00 am and 8:00 am.
检查完毕 没有追踪器
He is clean. There is no tracker.
如果你跟踪我们 桑德斯会再放毒
If you try to follow us, Saunders will release the virus.
韦恩·帕默尔
Wayne Palmer.
我是杰克·鲍尔
This is Jack Bauer
查佩尔的尸体已经被桑德斯的人拿走了
Chappelles body has just been picked up by Saunders' people.
谢谢你 杰克
Thanks Jack.
瑞恩·查佩尔死了
Ryan Chappelle is dead.
我下令杀了出类拔萃的探员
I ordered the death of one of our agents, one of our finest.
这太疯狂了
As unthinkable as that was,
但我必须为拯救平民的性命争取时间
I had to buy some time in order to protect civilian lives.
我不会再屈服于这种恐怖份子了
I will not cave in to any more of this terrorists demands.
大卫 很不幸 桑德斯持有病毒并声称要散播 我们根本没办法强硬起来
David, unfortunately we are vulnerable as long as Saunders has his virus and is willing to release it.
目前已有700余人感染病毒 他们很快会死去
So far, over 700 people have been infected, and they're all gonna die.
除非你能接受更多伤亡 我们仍然束手无策
Now, unless you are willing to accept more loss of life, I dont know what else we can do.
他逼得我们无路可退 大卫
He has us in a corner, David.
召集所有内阁成员
Convene the Cabinet.
是
Yes sir.
你发现了什么?
What did you find?
我们研究了查佩尔对资金流向的调查
We worked up the money trails that Chappelle had on his system.
斯蒂芬 桑德斯每月都会汇10000美金给他的女儿简
Stephen Saunders has been sending $10000 a month to his daughter Jane.
他有个女儿?
He has a daughter?
对 屏幕上这个就是
Yes. Right here on the screen.
她今年19岁 住在圣巴巴拉 在那上学
She is 19, she lives in Santa Barbara. She goes to school there.
好的 查查她现在在哪
All right, find out where she is now.
给圣巴巴拉警局打电话 请他们待命
Call Santa Barbara PD(Police Department), make sure they are on standby.
阿尔梅达
Almeida.
托尼 我是杰克
Tony, it's Jack.
杰克 怎么样?
Jack, what happened?
查佩尔死了
Chappelle is dead.
桑德斯的人带走了他的尸体
Saunders people picked up his body.
4个男人带着面罩 开一辆黑色货车 没牌照
4 men all wearing hoods, black van, no plates.
好吧 我看能不能从卫星上追踪到它
All right, look, I will see if we can SAT track it.
我已经让亚当办了
I already put Adam on it.
有没有搞明白桑德斯为什么想要查佩尔的命?
Do we have any idea why Saunders wanted Chappelle dead yet?
我正要打电话告诉你
I was just about to call you.
我们发现了查佩尔自己找到的线索
We found a thread that Chappelle was working up on his own.
桑德斯好像有个女儿
Looks like Saunders has a daughter.
女儿?
A daughter?
对 查佩尔调查资金动向 发现最终流向简 桑德斯
Yeah, the money trail Chappelle was following leads to a Jane Saunders.
有她的基本资料吗?
What do we know about her?
我们还在调查
We are still digging up information.
现在只获悉她今年19岁 在圣巴巴拉上学
We know she is 19 years old, she goes to school in Santa Barbara.
现在还在吗?
Is she still there?
对 我刚准备让圣巴巴拉警方把她带走
Yeah. I was just about to call the Santa Barbara office to have her picked up.
等等 托尼 托尼 不行 这样不行
Wait, Tony, Tony, don't. Thats not the right play.
为什么?
Why not?
你想想
Think about it.
我们对这女孩一无所知
We dont know anything about this girl.
我们不清楚她是否了解她父亲
We dont know if she even knows who her father really is.
但桑德斯会竭尽全力保护他女儿
And obviously Saunders is going to everything he can to protect his daughter.
那肯定有人在暗中盯着她
So someone is watching her.
如果你想把她带来问话
If you want to grab her for questioning,
你必须瞒天过海
you are going to have to do it without him knowing.
也就是说 得偷梁换柱 用我们的探员调包
Which means we have to conduct a plain sight swap, switch her out with one of our own agents.
杰克不知道能否来的及
Jack, I dont know that we have the time.
我们得在半小时内找到一个和这女孩相似的女探员
We are going to have to find an agent that looks like the girl within the next half hour.
现在桑德斯已经占据主动
Right now Saunders is calling all the shots.
如果再不抓紧 我们只能任他宰割
If we dont do something soon, we are going to be completely paralyzed.
好吧 我马上去办
All right, I will get started.
克萝伊 我们得找个和简 桑德斯长的像的人
Chloe, we need to find a Jane Saunders look alike.
拿她的体貌特征和反恐局2区和3区的所有探员对比
I need you to abstract a physical description cross referencing with our CTU agents in regions 2 and 3.
好 什么时候要?
Ok, when do you need it?
现在
Right now.
我刚开始调查她的资料
I just started the file on her.
克萝伊 求你了 帮我个忙
Chloe, just do it for me, please.
德斯勒.
Dessler
嘿 是我
Hey, it's me.
你的检测结果出来了吗?
Did you get the test results?
还没 可能还得一个小时
I won't know if I am infected for another hour.
怎么这么久?
Whats taking so long?
他们这里得不出结论
They couldnt interpret the result here.
他们得把所有资料传回实验室
They had to send everything back to the lab.
你感觉怎样?
How are you feeling?
我 我觉得还行
I am, I think I am ok.
没有流鼻血?
No nose bleeds?
皮肤没反应?
Nothing on your skin?
没有
No.
听着 卫生署的人已经控制住了这里
Look, NHS has everything under control here.
我不想闲着
I want to keep busy.
我能做点什么?
How can I help?
亚当正在做全城搜索
Adam is working on a citywide containment.
我让他移交一点工作给你
I will have him split off some of his workload on your system.
打开接口 你和卫生署的人能帮点忙
Open a socket, you can help with NHS deployment.
我过会打给你 好吗?
I will call you later, ok?
好 好的
Yeah, ok.
米歇尔还在酒店里
Michelle is still at the hotel.
我告诉她你会给她传些资料让她处理
I just told her you'd send over some of your system updates for her to work on.
好 我马上传给她
Ok, I will send them right over.
那个从酒店逃出去的家伙查的怎么样了?
Where are we on this guy who escaped from the hotel?
他叫比尔·科尔 是一名保险销售代表
His name is Bill Cole, he is an insurance sales rep.
我们和她妻子联系过 但她并不是很配合
We contacted his wife by phone, but she wasn't being very cooperative.
但她告诉我们科尔以前经常早出晚归
We did manage to get from her that Cole came home unusually late and left early.
去工作?
For work?
也许 但他们公司要半小时后才开门
Probably, but his office doesn't open for another half hour,
我们还在找他
so we are looking for him now.
卫生署的人刚到他家 他们会隔离那里并检测他妻子
NHS has just arrived and they will quarantine the house and test the wife.
谁过去的?
Who are we sending over there?
蔡斯 他很快会到
Chase. He will be there soon.
鲍尔探员 总统的电话
Agent Bauer, I have the President for you.
接过来
Patch him through.
杰克
Jack.
总统先生
Mr President.
斯蒂芬 桑德斯 那个持有病毒的人 你认识他 对吧?
Stephen Saunders, the man who is in control of the virus, you know him, correct?
是的先生 我和他在执行一项您批准的任务中合作过
Yes sir. I worked with him a number of years ago on a mission that you sanctioned.
科索沃的德拉赞任务
The Drazen mission in Kosovo.
上次他打电话来 他说有新的要求
The last conversation I had with him, he said there would be other demands.
他是这么说的 好戏就要上演
His exact words: the main event to come.
你知不知道他在暗示什么?
You have any idea what he means by that?
我不知道 先生
I wish I could tell you, sir.
现在斯蒂芬 桑德斯满脑子都是复仇
Right now Stephen Saunders is in a vengeful state of mind.
他的所有要求都会危及美国的安全
Any demands that he makes will be detrimental to American security.
我想知道 杰克 如果我对他说不会怎样?
What I am asking, Jack, is what will he do if I say no to him?
总统先生 我和他合作的时候 从没想过他会如此丧心病狂
Mr. President, when I worked with Stephen Saunders, I never thought he was capable of mass murder.
今天我们知道了
Today we know he is.
他手上还有病毒
He still has the virus.
如果你不满足他的要求 先生 我相信他会继续放毒
If you dont meet his demands, sir, I believe that he will continue to release it.
谢谢你 杰克
Thank you, Jack.
是 总统先生
Yes, Mr President.
这是和简 桑德斯相似度排在前10位的探员名单
Here is the list you wanted of the top ten agents that could double as Jane Saunders.
全都不在洛杉矶
None of these are in Los Angeles.
我知道 最近的在旧金山反恐局
I know. The closest is CTU San Francisco.
有没有备选名单?
Did you put together a 2nd tier list?
有
Yeah.
没弄错吧?
You sure this is right?
肯定 我看到结果后检查了两遍
Yeah, I double checked when I saw the results.
金 鲍尔
Kim Bauer.
金 到我办公室来下 好吗
Yeah, Kim, could you come up to my office, please.
好
Sure.
谢谢
Thanks.
你不考虑清楚就要用她?
You are not thinking of using her?
我们别无选择
We don't have a choice.
你是不是应该先和杰克说一下?
Shouldn't you talk to Jack first?
克萝伊 我会处理的 好吗? 谢谢
Chloe, I will take care of it, all right? Thank you.
坐吧
Why don't you sit down.
好
Ok.
金 我们得叫简 桑德斯来问话 但不能让他父亲知道
Kim, we need to question Jane Saunders without her father knowing about it.
问题是他肯定派人暗中盯着她
The problem is, we are pretty sure he has somebody watching her.
好吧 你想让我做什么?
Fine. What do you need me to do?
你们年龄相仿 体型相似
Well, you are the same age, similar body types,
只是面部特征不同 但若加以伪装从远处应该分辨不出
your facial fertures are different, but no so different that we couldn't disguise it from a distance.
你想让我假扮简 桑德斯
You want me to pose as Jane Saunders.
原本有更合适人选 但都离这太远
Well, we have better matches, but they are too far away from this office.
所以 没办法 你是我们最后的希望
So, the bottom line is, you are our best chance.
我们的时间不多了
Now, we don't have much time.
这个计划还未完善
We are still in the early stages of planning this mission,
但如果顺利的话 不会很危险
but if all goes according to plan, it shouldn't be too dangerous.
我不会强迫你去做的
No, I am not going to order you to do this.
我知道 我也知道今天都发生了什么
I know, and I know what's been going on today.
如果你有更好的选择 你早就选了
And if you had a better option, I know you'd take it.
我没事 我接受任务
So, I am fine and I will do it.
你肯定?
You sure?
我肯定
Positive.
克萝伊 我要去圣巴巴拉一下
Chloe, I am leaving for Santa Barbara in a few minutes,
你得把我的资料转移到你那里
so you are going to need to transfer all my stuff onto your system.
我都知道了 我已经传好了
I know everything that's happening, I already pulled your data.
很好
Good.
我得实话实说 我告诉过托尼派你去不合适
I think its only fair that I tell you. I told Tony I didnt think you should do this.
外勤任务不是你能应付的来的
Field work isnt learn as you go.
我不是要去做一名外勤探员 克萝伊 没别的人可选了
I am not doing this to be a field agent, Chloe, there is no one else.
对 这也是为何我没和托尼据理力争
Yeah, thats why I didnt fight Tony harder.
即使说了他也不会听
Not that he would listen to me anyway.
我总是被无视 他从不尊重我在战术部署上的意见
I am not so out of it that I don't know he doesn't respect my opinions on tactical matters.
听着 我得出发了
Ok, look, I have to go.
好吧我只想让你知道我的感受 我是为你好
Ok, I just wanted to let you know how I felt, and I want you to know that I am behind 110%.
我真心希望你平安无事
I really hope nothing bad happens to you.
听着 克萝伊 你负责这次行动的内部协调吗?
Listen, Chloe, are you coordinating this operation from inside?
对
Of course.
那好 也许你该准备一下了 肯定有一大堆探员正等你你去联络呢
Ok, maybe you should start prepping, because I bet there is about 2 dozen agents still waiting for comm. Codes.
你真是干劲十足 金 保持下去
I like your energy, Kim. Use it.
亚当 能给我这次简 桑德斯任务的人员名单么?
Adam, could you send me a list of all the personnel working on the Jan Saunders operation?
暂时不行 克萝伊 我正盯着蔡斯那边
I can't do it right now, Chloe, I am monitoring Chase.
他找到比尔·科尔了?
Did he find Bill Cole?
还没有 他正在询问科尔的妻子
Not yet, he is interrogating Cole's wife.
一切都乱套了
This thing is out of control.
我在电话里已经说过了比尔不在
I already told the people on the phone that Bill isn't here.
我知道 我知道
I know, I know,
但他在家的时候
but when he was here,
你有没有发现什么不对劲?
did you notice anything out of the ordinary?
比如有没有流鼻血?
Was he bleeding from the nose for instance?
没有 我没看到
No, not that I saw.
有没有皮疹或者皮肤过敏之类的?
What about rashes, skin irritation, anything of that sort?
没有 为什么你们会认为他患病了?
No. Why would you think that hed be sick?
他和钱德勒 广场酒店里患病的人有过接触
He came in contact with some people who are sick at the Chandler Plaza Hotel.
他什么时候去过钱德勒 广场酒店?
When was he at the Chandler Plaza?
今天凌晨
Earlier this morning.
不 不 他没有
No, no, he wasn't.
他在公司和客户谈工作
He was with a client at the office.
他又偷腥去了 是吗?
He did it again, didn't he?
这个混蛋老毛病又犯了
That bastard did it again.
女士
Maam.
我希望他染上点什么
Then I hope he did get something.
我希望他去死
I hope that he dies.
别这样 科尔夫人 我需要你的帮助
Please, Mrs Cole, I need you.
都出去 别拦我
Get out of here. Get out of my way.
科尔夫人
Mrs Cole.
别拦我
Get out of my way.
科尔夫人 你必须冷静 我不能让你离开
Mrs Cole, you need to stay calm, because I cant let you leave.
埃德蒙兹探员
Agent Edmunds.
什么事
Yeah.
我们人发现了这个
One of my men just found this.
在哪发现的?
Where?
卫生间的垃圾桶里
Wastebasket in the bathroom.
血迹还有些粘度 应该是新鲜的
Blood is tacky, which means its fresh.
这么说比尔·科尔已经发病了
Then Bill Cole is symptomatic.
对
Yeah.
马上联系方圆30里内的所有急救中心
I need you to contact every urgent care facility in a 30 mile radius.
是
Yes sir.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
我流了一个小时的鼻血了
I have had a nose bleed for about an hour.
怎么都止不住
I cant seem to stop it.
有没有用冰敷过?
Did you put ice on it?
有 但没用
Yeah. Didn't do anything.
去看下急诊吧
Try an ER, get it cauterized.
那太久了 我还得去上班
That will take too long. I got to go to work.
这儿没什么好办法
We dont have anything here that will stop that.
好吧 谢谢
All right. Thanks.
对不起
Excuse me.
我们准备在学校图书馆动手掉包
The swap will take place at the campus library.
她每天早上在那工作
She works there in the mornings.
这是相关的人员资料
This is a file of relevant personal data.
好的
All right.
克萝伊 托尼在哪?
Chloe, where is Tony?
他和金在远程会议室
He is in the teleconference room with Kim.
她怎么没和你一起做卫星追踪?
Why isn't she working the satellite track with you?
呃 你也许该和托尼谈谈
Uh, you might want to talk to Tony about that.
当你就位后 要表现的自然一点
When you get into the position, just act naturally.
尽量看着某个地方
Try to look up a place.
嘿 杰克
Hey, Jack.
你和金在这干什么?
What are you doing with Kim?
克萝伊收集了一份适合假扮简 桑德斯的人选名单
Chloe came over a list of potential matches for Jane Sanders.
很好 怎么样?
Good, so we have got one?
你可能会不高兴
Well, you are not going to like it.
是金
It's Kim.
我女儿金?
My Kim?
我也不想这样
I am not crazy about it either,
但她是唯一一个体型相似同时地理位置最近的
but she is the only one that matched both physically and geographically.
你不能派她去执行外勤任务
You are not sending her into the field.
她能胜任的而且很安全
She can handle it, plus she has a safety net.
让别人去 托尼
Find someone else, Tony.
杰克 你自己也这样说 我们要在桑德斯不知情的情况下接触他女儿
Jack, you said yourself, we need to get Saunder's daughter without him knowing.
金是最佳选择
Kim is our best shot at doing that.
她不能去
She is not doing it.
这不是你说了算 这是她自己的决定
It's not up to you, it's her decision.
行
Fine.
我会阻止她这样做
I will order her not to do it.
她不是为你工作 杰克
She doesn't work for you, Jack.
她替我工作
She works for me.
别...
Don't...
别这样 求求你
Please don't do this, please.
立刻给我出去
Get out of here now.
否则我把你踹出去 快走
Or I will throw you out myself. Move.
杰克
Jack.
你和你父亲好好谈谈
You talk it over with your father.
如果要放弃 尽快告诉我
If we have to abort this, I want to know now.
我就在外面
I will be outside.
我明白你觉得这么做是对的 但不行你不能去
I know you think you are doing the right thing, but this is not going to happen.
总得有人去
Somebody has to do it.
别人可以 你不行
Someone will, not you.
我是最佳人选
I am the best match.
你不是外勤人员
You are not a field operative.
我受过武器训练的 而且只是假扮一下
I have weapons training. This is decoy work.
金 你想的太简单了
Kim, you don't know what you are talking about.
如果所有的事跟你设想的一样 我也用不着去冒险
If everything was to go right in this scenario, which is not a chance I am willing to take.
这个险不用你冒 是我去
You are not taking it, I am
你得到这个工作的原因
The reason why you have got this job,
我让你做这个工作的原因是我要确保你的安全
the reason why I gave you this job is so that I an make sure you'd be safe.
我接受这份工作是因为我想要它
I took this job because I wanted it,
不是你想要我怎样
not because you wanted me here.
我知道对你来说很难接受
I know that this is hard for you,
但这不是你的决定
but this is not your decision.
这是我的工作 更准确的说 我的职责
This is my job, better yet, my duty.
我会平安无事的
I am going to be safe,
但我一定要去
but I am doing it.
他们准备好了?
They are ready to go?
一切就绪
All set.
好 我们到了之后 他们会给你准备假发和化妆
Ok, now as soon as we get there, they are going to deal with your hair and makeup.
记住 距离太近还是会露馅
Remember, we are not trying to fool anyone at close range.
你必须找个位置 让桑德斯的手下只能从远处看到你
You will be in a position where Saunders' people can only view you from a distance.
恩 正常
Oh, it's fine.
-金  -怎么了?
-Kim  -Yeah?
拿着这把枪
This is a gun I got for you.
但如果真有情况 千万别犹豫
but if you do, don't hesitate.
好的
Ok.
走 我们出发
Come on, let's go.
请坐
Please be seated.
非常抱歉匆忙召集诸位 感谢各位的配合
Thank you for assembling on short notice.
各位已经对科迪利亚病毒威胁的事有所了解了 它正威胁我们所在的城市
You have already been briefed on the Cordilla Virus that's now threatening our cities.
现在 有两个新情况
What you don't know is we have 2 new developments.
韦恩
Wayne.
第一 其中一管病毒已经被释放了
First, a vial of that virus has already been release.
洛杉矶的钱德勒 广场酒店是第一个遭受攻击的
The Chandler Plaza Hotel, here in Los Angeles, was the site of the first attack.
那里的形势暂时已控制住
That situation is being addressed.
第二 我们查出了幕后主谋
Secondly, we discovered the identity of the perpetrator.
他叫斯蒂芬 桑德斯 曾是英国军情6处的特工
His name is Stephen Saunders and he is a former MI6 agent.
现在 桑德斯手上至少还有11管病毒 他威胁称如果不满足他的要求 他将继续放毒
Now, apparently, Mr Saunders has at least 11 more vials and is threatening to release them unless we meet his demands.
总统先生 他提了什么要求?
Mr President, what are those demands?
到现在为止有两个
So far there have been 2.
第一个是让总统召开记者招待会 期间必须提及 "灭顶之灾" 这个词
The first was for the President to use the phrase "the sky is falling" in a press conference.
然后他要求我们杀死一名联邦探员
He then demanded that we terminate one of our own agents.
一名探员? 为什么?
One of our agents? Why?
我们还在查
Well, we are still looking into that.
你拒绝了他 他有什么反应?
What was his response when you didn't comply?
很遗憾 我除了妥协别无他法
It devastates me to tell you that I had no choice but to comply.
半小时前
A half hour ago,
我们将这位探员的尸体交给了桑德斯的手下
we delivered this agent's body to one of Saunders' representatives.
天哪
My God.
上百万的性命危如累卵
Millions of lives are at stake.
我要你们各个部门积极配合洛杉矶反恐局
I am going to need each of your departments to open your files to CTU Los Angeles.
给他们所要的一切
Give them whatever they need.
托尼 我要替杰克收集些国防部的资料 我需要查普尔的授权
Tony, I am trying to get into some DOD files for Jack, I need authorization from Cahppelle.
他什么时候回来?
When is he going to be back?
他不会回来了
He is not.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
各位 请听我说 好吗?
Could I have everybody's attention, please?
很抱歉告诉各位
I am sorry to tell you that,
瑞恩·查佩尔在半小时前因公殉职了
Ryan Chappelle was killed in the line of duty about a half an hour ago.
我不能透露更多的细节
I can't give you any more details,
但在分局的布拉德 哈蒙德下达指令前 我会接手他的工作
but I will be assuming Ryan's responsibilities until we hear from Brad Hammond at division.
也许各位会缅怀瑞恩
Now, there will be an opportunity to pay proper respects to Ryan,
但现在不是时候
but now is not the time.
托尼 蔡斯的电话 在5号线
Tony, it's Chase on line 5.
谢谢
Thanks.
阿尔梅达.
Almeida
是我 我在科尔的家里
Yeah, it's me. I am at Cole's house.
我们找到些证据 他可能已经发病了
We found evidence he is almost certainly symptomatic.
好吧 有多少人和他接触过?
All right, how many people did he come in contact with over there?
只有他的妻子
Just his wife.
卫生署的人正把她隔离起来
NHS is moving her into isolation right now.
好的 我通知其他人
All right, I will let the teams know.
托尼 帮我转接金 她帮我做了个模拟
Tony, transfer me to Kim. She was running a simulation for me.
好 我告诉亚当
Yeah, I gave that to Adam.
金外出执行任务了
Kim is out on assignment right now.
什么任务?
What kind of assignment?
我们肯定桑德斯会派人暗中监视他女儿
Well, we are pretty sure that Saunders has his daughter under surveillance,
所以我们准备在抓他女儿时 派金替换她
so Kim is gonna take her place when we grab her.
金又不是外勤探员
Kim is not a field ops.
你让她去干什么?
What the hell is she doing out there?
我不想听这个 蔡斯 好吗?
I don't want to hear about it, chase, all right?
金是我们现在唯一可用的
Kim was the only match we had available.
托尼 你肯定能找到其他人的
Tony, there is got to be other agents you can use for this.
你到底在想什么?
What the hell are you thinking?
不 没了
No, there aren't.
你别管 蔡斯
Back off, Chase.
她现在在哪?
Where is she now?
她和杰克一起 在去圣巴巴拉的路上
She is on her way to Santa Barbara with Jack.
杰克同意了?
Jack signed off on this?
首先 这是我的命令
First of all, it's my call.
其次 对 杰克同意了 但最重要的是 金接受了任务
Secondly, yes, Jack did, but most importantly, Kim accepted the assignment.
现在 我给你转接亚当
Now, I am gonna transfer you over to Adam.
好吧
Fine.
听着 我为之前的所为向你道歉
Look, I am sorry about what happened earlier about grabbing you.
我只是不觉得你这么做是对的
I just don't think what you are doing is right.
但我要你明白
But I need you to understand something.
待会任务由我指挥
in the field I am in command.
你必须按我说的做
You do what I tell you to do.
明白吗?
Do you understand me?
你明白了吗?
明白
Yes.
好的
Ok, good.
我的鼻子已经出血快一个小时了 就是止不住
My nose has been bleeding for almost an hour, and I can't get it to stop.
好的
All right.
先坐下 把这个填好
Have a seat and fill this out.
还要多久?
How long will that take?
谢谢
Thanks.
至于这种疾病的严重性
As to how serious this illness is,
我们尚未得知 官方暂无任何回答
we have no new information and the authorities are not commenting.
我们也无从证实 但据悉酒店里人们所感染的物质
We can't verify this but we are hearing that whatever is infecting the people of this hotel,
已有人见到装尸袋 钱德勒 广场酒店附近到处是救护人员的身影
Body bags have been spotted, and rescue workers are positioned around the Chandler Plaza.
官方未就此事作出任何反应...
Authority do not give any information regarding the estimated...
嘿
Hey.
请稍等 先生
One minute, sir.
不 现在
No, now.
我现在就要看医生
I need to see a doctor now.
我曾在那个酒店待过 我肯定染了什么很严重的病
I was at that hotel. There is something seriously wrong with me.
哦 上帝 你就是那个人
Oh, my god, you are him.
乔伊纳医生
Dr Joyner.
那个需要被隔离的人 在这
The man we are supposed to isolate, he is here.
请讲
Yes.
我们确认过尸体了
We have just identified the body.
是不是查佩尔?
And it's Chappelle?
是的 拇指指纹和档案上的相符
It's confirmed. The thumbprint matched the one in his file.
很好
Good.
-把尸体处理掉  -是
Dump the body. Yes, sir.
你的麻烦解决了?
You take care of your problem?
对 查佩尔死了
Yes, Chappelle is dead.
但反恐局会试图找出他所发现的
But CTU is still gonna try to find out what he was working up,
告诉伦诺克斯保持警觉
so tell Lennox to stay alert,
确保简在他的视线以内
make sure he doesn't let Jane out of his sight.
喂
Yeah.
有什么情况吗?
Any problems?
没有 她正准备离开住处
No. She is leaving her apartment now.
她要去工作了
She is going to work.
好的 跟着她
All right, stay with her.
接下来的几个小时非常关键
The next few hours are crucial.
我会注意的
I will be here.
总统先生 我们现在好像在坐滑梯 除非我们能...
Mr President, we have started down a slippery slope here, and unless we are...
别绕弯子了 约瑟夫 你想说什么?
Cut the euphemisms, Jeseph. What are you trying to say?
先生 我们对你授命杀死我们的一名高级情报人员感到担忧
Sir, we are concerned about the fact that you ordered the death of a high ranking member of our intelligence
我们根本就别无选择
I don't think we are here to second guess actions that have already been taken.
约瑟夫 这个决定多么残忍 没人比我清楚
Joseph, no one is more aware than I am of the moral ambiguity of my decision.
我必须得给反恐组争取时间来找出桑德斯
I did it to buy CTU more time to find Saunders
还有尽可能拖延这场大屠杀
and to delay for as long as possible the slaughter of millions.
我做这个决定是为了保护平民的未来
I made the decision to protect their future,
并非我个人的
not mine.
是桑德斯
Saunders.
我必须接
I have to take this.
说
Yes.
我已经确认了查佩尔的尸体 总统先生
I have confirmed the identity of Chappelle's body, Mr President.
他会被妥善处理
It will be disposed of respectfully.
我们已经清楚你的身份 桑德斯先生
We know who you are, Mr Saunders.
不管你有什么企图 都不会得逞的
Whatever you are trying to accomplish, you are going to fail.
你最好还是放弃这些病毒 祈祷别让我们找到你
Your only chance is to relinquish the virus and hope we don't find you.
这不可能
That's not going to happen.
你想怎么样?
What is it you want?
让美国回归净土
To make America clean again.
你也知道 总统先生
You see, Mr President.
全世界都仇视美国
the world hates America
种种原因
and for good reason
在此我就不细说了 对于你的国家曾实施的暴行 相信你比我更清楚
I won't bother going into the details, you know better than I the atrocities your nation commits.
我们要改变这一切
But we are going to change all that.
你和我 将一起 把这个恶行遍布全球的战争机器消灭
You and I, together, are going to dismantle the military machine that exports its ugliness across the globe.
你想怎么做?
And how are we going to do that?
我们先从我略有所知的那些最肮脏的活动下手
We will start where the work gets the dirtiest, something I know a little about.
国外秘密活动
Covert foreign nationals.
在中东及亚洲的近30个国家里
In 32 countries across the Middle East and Asia,
你们的政府都雇有A级到H级的情报人员
your government employs grade A through H intelligence consultants.
他们是那些国家的公民
They are citizens of the countries in which they reside.
他们是间谍
They are spies.
听从美国这个战争机器的吩咐和自己的国家作对
Working against those countries at the behest of the American military machine.
在45分钟内 我要你把他们的身份通过
In 45 minutes, I want a list of their identities sent to me by way of a web site
Sylviaimports.com 传给我
Sylviaimports.com
如果你不从
If you fail to cmply,
我会在主要城市散播两管病毒
I will release 2 vials of the virus in major cities.
而这次
And this time,
就不会在酒店这种容易控制的地方了
they won't be in hotels where they can be contained.
鲍尔探员 我是雷切尔·弗雷斯特
Agent Bauer, Rachel Forrester.
这位是探员金 鲍尔 她是我们准备替换简 桑德斯的人选
This is Agent Kim Bauer. She is gonna be doubling for Jana Saunders.
我们已经在她工作的图书馆外选好了指挥点
We have already set up a staging area outside the library where she works.
是否安全?
Is it a safe distance away?
-她已经到了?  -还没有 但快到了
-Is she there yet?  -No. She will be in a few minutes.
我们走 出发吧
Let's go ahead. Let's go.
确保通知这个街区上的所有人 不要离开所处的房屋
Make sure everybody on the block is contacted and nobody leaves their house.
谢里夫他们已经派人到这3个街区内巡逻 在他们到之前
Sheriff's department is sending officers over to patrol a 3 block area until they get here.
你们先负责
Use your men.
失陪
Excuse me.
埃德蒙兹.
Edmunds
找到比尔·科尔了
Yeah, we found Bill Cole.
-在哪?  -在离你不远的一个急诊中心
-Where?  -He is at an urgent care center not far from you.
在月桂峡谷大道和穆尔帕克大道附近
Laurel Canyon and Moorpark.
嗯 我知道在哪
Yeah, I know where that is.
我要你赶到那 从科尔那得到尽可能多的信息
I want you to get over there, get as much as you can off of Cole.
他情绪很不稳定 你得让他冷静下来
He is pretty agitated, you are gonna have to help him focus.
-托尼  -嗯
-Tony.  -Yeah.
金已经在执行任务了?
Is Kim in play yet?
还没 她刚刚在圣巴巴拉着陆
No. She just landed in Santa Barbara.
好的 再联络
All right, I will call you.
简现在在哪?
Where is Jane now?
我们的人正在图书馆里密切关注她
My people have her under surveillance in the library
她正在咨询台工作
working behind the reference desk.
里面有多少人?
How crowded?
10到20个
10, 20 people.
这些人里有桑德斯的人
Well, one of them belongs to Saunders,
他们肯定受命不让她离开他们的视线
and their orders are gonna be not let her out of their sight, not for one second.
我知道 我们已经控制了监控摄像头
I know. We have taken over the surveillance cameras
范围已经缩小到5个人
and we have narrowed down a list to about 5 probables.
好的 把这些情报传给反恐局的托尼·阿尔梅达
Ok, get that intel over to Tony Almeida at CTU.
好了 让我看看
Ok, let's see her.
好的 记住 金
Ok, now remember, Kim
你这样在近距离没法骗过熟悉简 桑德斯的人
You are not gonna fool anyone who knows Jane Saunders up close.
我知道
I know.
其他人都清楚自己的任务
The staff knows what's happening.
我要你和前台保持10英尺的距离
But I want you to stay at least 10 feet behind the counter,
尽量不要抬头
and I want you to keep your head down as much as possible.
这个假发看起来比简的头发颜色深
the wig looks darker than Jane's hair color.
这么短的时间里 只能找到这么接近的
That's the best we could do on such short notice.
你们得在细节上做足工夫 这和她的安危息息相关
You are gonna have to match every detail as closely as possible, her life depends on it.
科尔先生 你在药店的时候 你和什么人有过接触?
Mr Cole, when you were inside the store, who did you come in contact with?
什么意思 接触?
What do you mean, contact?
和谁说过话?
Who did you talk to?
只有药架后面的配药师
Just the pharmacist behind the counter.
其他人呢?
How many others?
其他顾客?
Customers?
对 当时还有其他人在
Yeah, there were some other people there.
有多少个?
How many other people were there?
比尔.
Bill
如果不能找到这些你所接触过的人 病毒就会蔓延到整个城市
If we do not identify and track down everyone you have come in contact with, we are gonna have a citywide epidemic.
到底有多少人?
So how many people?
我 我不知道
I, I don't know.
仔细想想!
Think!
就是这个 现在解除系统防御
That's it. We are now patched against security.
音频缺失
No audio from the system.
B区正常
Nothing on B.
继续 看下6号
Go ahead, try six
这个视野和前台不相连
This screen go ahead isolate front desk.
5个够了
5 is good.
谢谢
Thank You.
哦
Oh.
非常抱歉
I am so sorry.
这里不准喝饮料
You are not supposed to have drinks in here.
对不起 我马上丢掉
I am sorry, I will throw it away.
没关系
It's ok.
注意那个穿红衣服的男人
Start tracking that man in the red shirt.
-注意他的一切动向  -是
-I want to know everything that he does.  -Yes Sir.
目标在4号机视野内
Subject is on camera 4 right now.
我正准备更换这些纸巾
I was just about to replace those.
给你
Here you go.
好了
Clear.
怎么搞这么久?
What the hell is taking her so long?
检查所有探头
Checking all surveillances now.
-1号机正常 2号机正常  -快啊
-Nothing on 1, nothing on 2.  -Come on.
先生 他在4号机视野出现
Sir, she came out from 4.
金.
Kim
书架旁有个男人
There is a man handing
towards the bookcase
你右侧3点钟位置 穿红衣服的
at your 3 o'clock, red shirt.
他可能是桑德斯的手下
Might be one of Saunders' men.
慢慢的远离他的视线
I want you to angle away from him slowly.
很好
Good.
我们刚从蔡斯那得知科尔接触过的人的信息
We just got off the phone with Chase who is with Cole right now.
科尔离开酒店后 回到了在伯班克的家中
After Cole left the hotel, he went to his house in Burbank.
其间在环河路的加油站停留片刻
He stopped at a gas station on Riverside Drive.
但那里是自助服务的
But it was self service.
据他在急诊室所言与他妻子那里的了解 证实他在到家后才出现病征
and according to what he told the urgent care unit what his wife confirmed, he didn't become symptomatic until after he got home.
-流鼻血 出虚汗?  -对
-The nose bleeds and the sweating?  -Right.
这是整个扩散过程
Here is where the ripple effect starts.
7点20分 他在药房逗留
At 7:20, he stopped at a pharmacy
向配药师山姆·泰勒询问止血药的位置
and asked the pharmacist Sam Tyler for some medication to stoop the bleeding
当时药房还有3个人
There were 3 other people inside that pharmacy at the same time
对 其中一名 安妮·施瓦兹
Right. One of them, Anne Schwartz.
她很多年都是在这个药房配药 那里有她的住址记录
She's has been going to the pharmacy for years, so they had her address on file.
已经通知卫生署的人到她家去
We have sent NHS people to her house.
她家还有丈夫和3个孩子
She has a husband and 3 children.
-其余两个呢?  -尚未确定身份
-What about the other 2 customers?  -ID is unknown.
他们可能出现在任何地方 将病毒传染给接触的人
These people could be anywhere, spreading the disease to anybody they come into contact with.
情况越来越糟
It gets worse.
还有那个急诊中心
At the urgent care facility in Studio City,
当时候诊区有6个病人
there were 6 patients in the waiting area.
科尔进来的时候 在警戒尚未设好前离开
when cole came in, who left before the quarantine was put in place.
我们还在追查这些人
We are tracking them down.
加上他们和急诊中心工作人员
But between them and the staff at the facility(TBD)
我们要找的人起码有75个
We could be looking at up to 75 people.
以及他们的亲属 如果他们中的任何一个在超市或者商场发病
Just in their immediate families. If any of these people are in a supermarket or a mall when they become symptomatic.
事情将会无法控制
This thing is going to be impossible to contain.
我们得确定他们的身份 尽快找到他们
We need to identify and find them now.
还有 我要你和卫生署与危险品紧急处理小组协调
Also, I need you to coordinate with NHS and HazMat.
我们得在伯班克社区附近设置警戒隔离
We have to set up a quarantine in 2 neighborhoods in the Burbank Studio City area.
有什么情况向亚当汇报
Department heads report to Adam.
干的好 伙计们 看起来任务成功了
Good work, everybody, it looks like this worked.
-继续观察金 有什么情况通知我  -明白
-Maintain monitering Kim. Come get me if anything happens.  -I got it.
谢谢 干的不错
Thank you, good work.
发生什么了?
What's going on?
你是谁?
Who are you?
我叫杰克·鲍尔 我是一名联邦探员
My name is Jack Bauer, I am a federal agent.
你现在很安全
You are not in any danger.
你想干什么?
What do you want?
我们需要你的帮助
We need your help
我们得找到你父亲
We need to get in touch with your father.
那你们去找啊 你们抓我来干什么?
Then get in touch with him. What do you need me for?
我们不知道他在哪
We don't know where he is.
我们认为你知道
and we think you do.
这都怎么回事?
What's this about?
你根本不知道你父亲是什么样的人
You don't know who your father really is.
首先 我对他了解也不多
First of all, I hardly know my father.
其次 不管怎样 你们这么做是违法的
And whatever this is, I know it's illegal.
你们不能把我关在这
You have no right to keep me here.
放了我 我没犯法
Release me now, I haven't done anything wrong
你最好听清楚了 简
You'd better listen to me very carefully, Jane.
你父亲正参与一项针对美国的恐怖主义行动
Right now your father is engaged in terrorist activity against the United States of America.
今天早上他已杀了上百人 他正威胁杀更多的人
This morning, he killed hundreds of people, and he is threatening to kill thousands more.
我知道你肯定接受不了这事实
Now, I can only imaging how difficult this must be for you to believe,
但你必须相信我 然后配合我们的工作
but trust me, you are going to cooperate with us.
很多人尚处在危险之中 留给我们的时间不多了
There is a lot at stake, and there is not a lot of time.
我什么也不会说 我要见律师
I am not going to do anything. I want to talk to a lawyer.
这里不会有律师
There is no lawyer.
只有你和我
There is just you and me.
我对我父亲一无所知
I don't know anything about my father.
他每年只来两三次 我们一起吃个饭什么的
He comes into town twice a year. I have dinner with him.
你怎么和他联系?
How do you contact him?
从没联系 都是他打我电话
I don't. He calls me.
-你撒谎 简  -我没有
-You are lying to me, Jane.  -I'm not
别想护着他 你这是给自己找麻烦
Don't try to protect him. You are just going to get yourself in a world of trouble.
你才有麻烦呢 你才是违法的人
You are the one in trouble here. You are the one breaking the law.
你以为我在跟你开玩笑?
You think I am playing a game here with you?
成千上万的人性命危在旦夕
Hundreds of thousands of people's
lives are on the line.
为了让你合作 我什么都做得出
You have no idea how far I am willing to go to acquire your cooperation.
你想对我作什么?
What are you threatening to do to me?
你父亲在哪 简?
Where is your father, Jane?
我不知道!
I don't know!
-你父亲在哪?  -来人啊 救救我
-Where is your father?  -Somebody, help me, pleaase
-杰克  -什么事?
-Jack  -What?
红衣服的男子正在靠近她
Red shirt is approaching her desk.
-怎么了? - 他在问询台那里
-What's going on?  -He's at the desk.
金 别转身 别动
Kim, don't turn around. Just stay where you are.
-图书管理员去跑哪去了?  -爱丽丝 派人到问询台去
-Where the hell is the librarian?  -Alice, get someone to the reference desk now.
-打扰一下  -请等一下
-Excuse me.  -Just a minute.
我 我想找本书
I, I need some help with, finding a book.
稍等
Just one second.
-好的 宝贝 做的很好...  -不要慌 我们正在查这个人
-Ok, sweetheart, you are doing great...  -Jus stay calm, until we check this guy out.
拉近镜头 注意问询台那个红衣服的男人
Give me a close up on the gentleman in the red shirt at the desk.
能帮帮我吗?
Can I get some help here?
我一会就好
I'll be with you in a minute.
好 金 慢慢的站起来 走到面前的书架那边去
Ok, Kim, I want you to slowly get up and try to make your way to the bookshelves in front of you.
在我们查出他是谁之前 先躲开他
Stay out of his eye line until we find out who this guy is.
-3号监控器一直盯着她  -将3号探头对准金
-Maintain a constant visual on her from monitor 3.  -Get camera 3 on Kim.
-我们找不到她了  -换个角度
We are panning off her. Get me another angle.
视野只有这么宽
There is no other angle.
-怎么回事?  -杰克 刚才还看到她 3号探头应该很快能找回她
-What's going on?  -Jack, we had her a second ago. Camera 3 should be panning back on her in few seconds.
-你在这工作 对吧?  -对
-You work here, don't you?  -Yeah.
-你能帮我找些书吗?  -可以 没问题 你想要什么?
-Could you help me find something in this aisle?  -Yeah, no problem. What is it that you need?
你敢呼救我就杀了你
You call for help, I will kill you right now.
谁抓走了简 桑德斯? 谁抓走了简 桑德斯?
Who has Jan Saunders? Who has Jan Saunders?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you are talking about.
她跑哪去了? 金!
Where the hell is she? Kim!
该死的
Damn it.
第二组 上 上
Team two, go, go
趴下 趴下
Get down, get down.
金.
Kim
金 退后 退后
Kim, step back, step back.
回复指挥台 目标已被击倒
Radio back. Tell them the subject is down.
-你没事吧  -没事
Are you ok? Yeah, fine.
桑德斯很快会知道我们抓了她女儿
Saunders is going to know we have his daughter.